So you can't cover much, I believe
in Bharatiya Jan Sangh, health insurance is
very important in today's time, otherwise what if
you saved money, I know, I
worked very hard, I don't know what all,
and you even saved a lot of money, by working for 10 years, let's say, you saved
10-20 lakh rupees, you saved it
somehow, and if
someone gets sick, this money will start getting exhausted, for a
week, ten days, 15 days, how many
people are practically able to talk to the patient on WhatsApp, are
able to do everything, and if
you have a little illness, you are able to
relax, but yes, there are
people who have taken 10 health
insurances, oh, I think you might have taken it just
for your name,
how much is known,
because if you take more cover, you do
n't have to pay a lot of premium, there is an
extra cover, in which the
whole family is covered, whether you, your
life, your children, all are covered,
this is called health insurance, medical
insurance, it must be there,
what happens in those
who do not get any last minute cleaning done
because you  We can leave
this topic, if something happens to us or ourselves, then
we cannot say that
we die, so what happens in such a situation, a lot of money is lost due to this, what else gets lost
very fast
and what happens is
taking a loan, you will have to take it very generously,
what does it mean to hide the improvement, that
you can never set it again in life,
how big is the problem of understanding this
and how complicated is it that
you will never be able to add money in life, that whatever you
earn will be spent, we
think that now people are from bank account
or from friends, from here, from here, if you do
not give it back to all the people, you will
spoil the friendship,
and one more thing, which has come till here, one more
thing, one more mistake we make is want to
make money, always stay away from it, wherever you are
thinking that invest this much money, you will get this much
money in this much time,
this will go, run away from there, turn around and run away from
here, do not stop by mistake, many such
schemes are running in the market
and unlimited and crores of people have invested their
money  We have earned and are in these circles,
now let us come to each other that
when did we add the money smartly, when did
we not block the money at unnecessary places,
so that if you take any endowment
insurance plan where your annual sum is
going to Rs. 50,000, then Rs. 50,000 becomes a
problem for 20 years, you understand, so
we played smartly here, got term
insurance, saved money from there, so what should
we do with the money that is saved now